https://www.jelcoinc.com/jelco-inc-privacy-policy/

Created with Sketch.
Created with Sketch.
Login
Forgot your password?
JELCO, INC. Privacy Policy
JELCO, INC. (JELCO) and its affiliates are very aware that privacy and the protection of personal information are concerns for many users of the Internet.
Personal Information
The security of your personal information is important to us. Therefore, we do not sell or rent your personal information to any third parties. Placing an Order
In order to create an account and/or place an order on www.jelcoinc.com, you must provide us with certain personal information such as your name, your credit card number and expiration date, your credit card billing address, your telephone number, your e-mail address and the name and shipping address of the recipient, if different. We require this information so that we can verify your status as a User, JELCO Reseller, Government or Education buyer, as applicable, and therefore offer you with appropriate pricing as well as process and fulfill your order.Promotional Email Subscription and Opt-Out Policy
JELCO's email newsletters and surveys are optional benefits you may choose to subscribe to that keep you up to date with the latest product launches and promotions.   JELCO values opinions and comments from our customers, so we periodically conduct email surveys. Participation in these surveys is entirely optional. Typically, the information is aggregated and used to gain feedback on new products, and to develop appealing content, features and promotions on the website. Survey participants are anonymous unless otherwise stated in the survey.
You can unsubscribe at any time from our email newsletters and surveys by choosing the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email.
Online SecurityAll personal information you provide to JELCO is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us.
Cookies"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies allow us to serve you better and more efficiently, and to personalize your experience at our site. Cookies also allow for faster access to pages that you may have already have visited. None of this information is passed to any third party and is used solely by us to provide you with a better user experience on our web site.
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies. By changing the options on your web browser or using certain software programs, you can control how and whether cookies will be accepted by your browser. JELCO supports your right to block any unwanted Internet activity, especially that of unscrupulous websites. However, blocking JELCO's cookies may disable certain features on our site and may make it impossible to purchase or use certain services available on the site. Please note that it is possible to block cookie activity from certain web sites while permitting cookies from sites you trust, like JELCO's.
JELCO's web site offers links to other Internet sites. We make every effort to link only to other sites that share a respect for web site users' privacy. However, JELCO is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these other sites.
JELCO reserves the right to change this policy at any time and will immediately post a revised and updated policy.
×
